We'll be right back.
Capture Robin, the determination of the Straw Hats.
Hold it right there!
Don't let him get away!
This is all your fault, Zoro!
The whole town is out looking for us.
It was gonna happen sooner or later, wasn't it?
You can't run forever!
This way!
Right!
Over here!
Where'd they go?
Check the alleys!
You don't think they're on the rooftops, do you?
Damn it!
We lost them!
I don't get it.
I'm sure they went this way.
We better keep moving.
All right, but we should check inside the buildings, too.
Good!
We'll split up!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Is it okay now?
Wait a sec.
Where'd you last see them?
Just a little longer.
Hmm?
What's that?
I'm begging you.
Are you crazy?
I gotta evacuate.
Stop pestering me.
Come on.
I have money, okay?
Here, take it.
I need as much lumber, tar, and rope as this will buy.
Oh, and also some nails, latches, and tin plates, if you don't mind.
I said I'm closing the shop.
It'll just take a second.
Please.
Okay, kid.
But I'm afraid this money ain't gonna buy much for you.
Uh, then...
How about I sell my tools?
Will that make up for the rest?
Hey, hey!
Come on, stop it.
We don't do barter.
This is the big city, you know.
I'm sorry, but it's cash only.
You win.
But let's make it quick.
You sure you're okay carrying that with all those injuries?
Can't you get some friends to help you out?
Hey!
I knew this was a bad idea.
Wait, this isn't gonna work.
I'm fine.
I got it.
This is nothing.
Hey!
Don't worry.
I can do it.
No, look.
Here, take these.
You're hungry, right?
Thank you.
Sure thing.
Try to be careful.
Good luck out there, kid.
Mmm.
These are good.
Really good.
Guess that guy was pretty nice after all.
The waves sure are getting high, aren't they?
Don't worry, Mary.
You're gonna be just fine.
After all, you flew in the sky, remember?
You got nothing to be afraid of.
No, no.
Oh, oh, oh.
Whoa.
What's got you riled up, big guy?
Gotta cry.
Oops.
Thank you.
Thanks, mate.
Come on, Frankie, you can tell us.
What's up, bro?
I got so much rage inside me, I feel another rampage coming on right about now.
Hey, wait for me, bro. Don't rampage alone.
As always, thanks for the drinks, Bluno.
What got into him all of a sudden? Is there something going on?
Beats me. Never can tell with that guy. Only idiots know what idiots are thinking.
Looks like the crowd cleared out.
Yeah, no thanks to you.
I'll have you know that Luffy and I had a perfectly good hiding place until you led that angry mob straight to us.
Like I said, with that many people looking, they were going to find you anyway.
Oh yeah, that reminds me. How'd you know we were down there, Chopper?
Your smell?
Ah, should have known. But wait, wasn't Sanji with you?
Well, he was.
No way! That doesn't make any sense! Did Robin really say that to you?
We were prepared for this, weren't we?
After all, Robin was our enemy before we let her join the crew.
This might be our only chance to find out the truth, so we shouldn't run away.
There's still a lot of things we don't know about Robin.
Now it's time to decide if she's a friend or a foe.
The situation will get worse.
From this day forward, we will never see each other again.
If she says she won't see us after today and things are going to get worse,
maybe that means the attack on Iceberg was just a warm-up
and she has something even bigger planned for tonight.
I don't know why Robin's doing any of this,
so it's hard to make a guess as to what she's planning.
But seeing how much commotion her first attack on the mayor caused,
there's only one way to make things worse.
In other words, she'll murder him.
I think that's what she's trying to tell us, at least.
Also, since she told Chopper that she'll be pinning the crime on us,
it could be that she's feeding us all these little hints
to try and lure us out to the crime scene tonight.
Think so?
If that is her plan, it would be convenient for her
if we did happen to show up,
since that would put us at the scene of the crime.
You say you don't know what she's thinking,
but it sounds to me like you've already decided that she's our enemy!
I'm talking about possibilities here, that's all.
We should always be prepared for the worst-case scenario, understand?
If I get locked into a single line of thinking,
it'll only slow me down.
If she's my friend, I have to be ready to forgive.
But if she's my enemy, I have to be ready to fight.
Our best chance to settle this is tonight.
Are we going?
Of course.
It's not that I object to the plan,
but we're still forgetting something.
Sanji said he saw Robin walking with someone in a mask, remember?
Obviously, that wasn't one of us,
but Iceberg said exactly the same thing,
that he was attacked by Robin and a large man in a mask
that he didn't recognize.
Whoever he is, I bet he's the reason
Robin is doing all of this stuff.
Yeah, that means it isn't our fault
and we just need to be the real bad guy, right?
That's the ideal situation.
But on the other hand,
it's also possible that this guy is one of Robin's friends.
The problem is, we don't have much to go on
other than a big man in a mask.
So where do we even start?
I mean, what is our goal here?
We find Robin and capture her.
That's the only way we'll ever know the truth.
You're right.
We're wasting time here trying to figure it out.
Just one thing,
Robin won't be easy to catch.
After all, the world government's been trying for 20 years
and it still hasn't happened.
Like he said,
it's the only way we'll really know for sure.
Yeah, let's settle this right now.
Right.
Come on, Gallylaw's waiting.
Damn, it's late.
Where'd that straw hat run off to?
Paulie, we gotta go.
All these streets are gonna flood before long.
All right, let's head back.
I'm going to the main office.
Sounds good, boss.
You heard him, guys.
Time to move out.
Get out here and fight me, straw hat!
Where are you?
Stop hiding!
I thought that little turd had some backbone,
but I guess I was wrong.
Won't even show his face.
I know what you're saying, bro,
but to be fair,
the whole island is hunting him down right now, you know?
Exactly.
I bet he's hiding if he hasn't been caught already.
By the way,
what's with this weird crab walk thing all of a sudden?
If we face the front,
then the wind catches our hair,
and we blow away!
Speaking of which,
the weather isn't the only thing that's out of control today.
Tell me about it.
It's like you've got a rampage going on inside you, too.
Shut up.
I'm just like that this week, okay?
Hey!
Bro!
Hey, it's Bro!
Hey, Bro!
Well, if it isn't, Zambai...
Tell me!
Tell me that you beat up those stupid straw hats!
Yeah, but I tried to.
Some angry mops showed up,
got in the way,
then Luffy took off.
Are those guys lucky or what?
When you're on a rampage,
nobody survives!
That's weird.
I wondered why that weak dude
with the long nose
was fixing the ship on his own.
I figured that you'd wrecked up
the rest of the crew so bad
that he was the only one left
who could do anything.
Wait,
you found one of them?
Yeah!
On their ship!
Well, that's just fine,
because all we need is one.
In other words,
we'll use that loser as bait
to lure out the rest of them.
Whoa!
Bro's got his bad guy face on, guys!
All right, you good-for-nothings.
I want you to march through the town
and spread the word for me.
Say,
we've got Long Nose,
and if you don't want him
swimming with the fishes,
then come to the warehouse
under the bridge.
Tell him
Frankie
sent ya.
In the meantime,
I'll go nab Long Nose
so we can make good
on our little threat.
You get it, bro!
I swear
we won't let you down!
Hey, you!
Yeah, you with the luggage.
What's all that stuff you got?
It's my special bed.
Aqualaguda!
疲れ果てた向きの中でも変わらないもの探すコンバスで いつまでも持っていれるから
いつか辿り着く夢の終わりに できるだけこのままで大人に
見上げた果てしないこの大空に 永遠に 永遠に
幼き頃の夢物語 忘られち記憶の糸辿り 未だ胸を焦がす残り火を消してしまわないように
乱れた羽渡るこの空に 仲間と共に想いを託し 移り変わる時代を越え 永遠に 永遠に
大空の現実に とりもしてない オンスメイル オンスメイル ウじゃあ ロインの世界が大光に 鬼が作わなかった
アンダーマまだ同じですが 君がなんだ
ロインを の六枚が見られるの?".
さしては自分ない鍵を 見ることや
大那には コンフィスのステッチから オンスの始めは Voyagerに コンフィス分  As violenceに、
タルコ期のワイヤー菌を取り集めて IP-9が行く
間違えた delle千々がさげよう
ワチフォームをとった